================================================================
License Agreement for Setup Utility Tools
================================================================

1. PROPRIETARY RIGHTS: Title, ownership rights, and intellectual
   property rights in the SOFTWARE shall remain in Fuji Xerox and
   its third party suppliers.  You have no rights in the SOFTWARE
   except as expressly granted in accordance with this agreement.
   
2. LICENSE:  Under this agreement, you are granted a non-exclusive
   license to use the SOFTWARE for the purpose of using with
   compatible Fuji Xerox products in your country.  You are not permitted to
   (1) assign, sublicense, sell, rent, lease, convey, or transfer the
   SOFTWARE to any third party by any tangible media such as floppy
   disk, magnetic tape, or CD-ROM, (2) distribute the SOFTWARE on a 
   network or by a telephone line available to the public or (3) 
   alter, modify, decompile, disassemble, reverse engineer, or create
   derivative works based on the whole or any part of the SOFTWARE.
   If any direction on usage or restriction for the SOFTWARE is 
   expressly specified in this web site, you are required to follow
   such direction.
   
3. TERM: This agreement is effective upon installing the SOFTWARE
   until you terminate the agreement by destroying the SOFTWARE. 
   This agreement will also terminate if you fail to abide by any 
   terms of this agreement.  In case of termination, you must
   promptly destroy the SOFTWARE.
   
4. LIMITED WARRANTIES: THE SOFTWARE IS SUPPLIED STRICTLY ON AN
   'AS IS' BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR
   IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTY OF
   MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WITH RESPECT
   TO THE SOFTWARE. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR CHOOSING, MAINTAINING AND
   MATCHING OTHER HARDWARE AND SOFTWARE COMPONENTS IN COMBINATION OF
   THE SOFTWARE.  IN NO EVENT, SHALL FUJI XEROX, FUJI XEROX CHANNEL
   PARTNERS, AUTHORIZED DEALERS AND THEIR THIRD PARTY SUPPLIERS BE
   LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE INCLUDING INCIDENTAL OR
   CONSEQUENTIAL LOSS OR DAMAGE, ARISING FROM USE OF OR INABILITY TO
   USE SOFTWARE, OR ANY MODIFICATION OF THE SOFTWARE.
   
5. EXPORT CONTROL: You are not allowed to export the SOFTWARE in part
   or whole, directly or indirectly, in violation of any 
   restrictions, laws or regulations imposed by the government of
   your country or any other relevant countries, and are required to obtain
   necessary approval prior to exporting the SOFTWARE.

=====================================================================
Additional Information:Setup Utility Tools Ver. 3.8.50
=====================================================================

This document provides information about the tools on the following 
items:
1. Tools Configuration
2. Prerequisites
3. File Configuration
4. Version Improvements
5. Cautions/Limitations
6. Inquiries

----------------------
1. Tools Configuration
----------------------
The Setup Utility Tools consist of the following 5 different tools:

* Upgrade Tool (Verup.exe)
  Upgrades the driver from an old version to a newer version. 

* Uninstallation Tool (UnInst.exe)
  Deletes the selected print driver from the system.

* Icon Deletion Tool (DelPrn.exe)
  Deletes the printer icon from the printer folder.

* Setup Disk Creation Tool (Makedisk.exe)
  Creates a setup disk for copying the driver installation 
  configuration in one computer, and installing the same 
  configuration into other computers.

* Setup Tool (UserSetup.exe / Setup.exe)
  Installs the driver with the same configuration stored in the setup
  disk.

----------------
2. Prerequisites
----------------
The tools operate on computers running with the following OS:

	Microsoft(R) Windows(R) 2000
	Microsoft(R) Windows(R) XP
	Microsoft(R) Windows(R) XP x64 Edition
	Microsoft(R) Windows Vista(R)
	Microsoft(R) Windows Vista(R) 64-bit Editions
	Microsoft(R) Windows(R) 7
	Microsoft(R) Windows(R) 7 64-bit Editions
	Microsoft(R) Windows(R) 8
	Microsoft(R) Windows(R) 8 64-bit Editions
	Microsoft(R) Windows(R) 8.1
	Microsoft(R) Windows(R) 8.1 64-bit Editions
	Microsoft(R) Windows(R) 10
	Microsoft(R) Windows(R) 10 64-bit Editions
	Microsoft(R) Windows Server(R) 2003
	Microsoft(R) Windows Server(R) 2003 x64 Editions
	Microsoft(R) Windows Server(R) 2008 (*)
	Microsoft(R) Windows Server(R) 2008 64-bit Editions (*)
	Microsoft(R) Windows Server(R) 2008 R2 (*)
	Microsoft(R) Windows Server(R) 2012 (*)
	Microsoft(R) Windows Server(R) 2012 R2 (*)

Please visit our web site to check the latest software and supported
operating systems.
        
        (*) Not supported when Server Core is installed.

* When using "Uninstallation Tool" under Windows Vista(R), Windows(R) 7, Windows(R) 8, Windows(R) 8.1, Windows(R) 10, 
  Windows Server(R) 2008, Windows Server(R) 2008 R2, Windows Server(R) 2012, or Windows Server(R) 2012 R2 
  please refer to items under "5. Cautions/Limitations".
  About driver deleting method (When using Windows Vista(R), Windows(R) 7, Windows(R) 8, Windows(R) 8.1, Windows(R) 10, 
  Windows Server(R) 2008, Windows Server(R) 2008 R2, Windows Server(R) 2012, or Windows Server(R) 2012 R2 ).


* When using Windows NT(R) Server 4.0 Terminal Server Edition, Windows(R) 2000   
  Server Terminal Service, Windows Server(R) 2003, Windows Server(R) 2008, Windows Server(R) 2008 R2, Windows Server(R) 2012 or Windows Server(R) 2012 R2
  Terminal Service, please execute Setup Utility Tools with installation mode.

  Please execute Setup Utility Tools with installation mode according to the
  following step.
  Open "Add or Remove programs" in "Control Panel" and then execute Setup
  Utility Tools.

* When using Windows Vista(R), Windows(R) 7, Windows(R) 8, Windows(R) 8.1, Windows(R) 10, 
  Windows Server(R) 2008, Windows Server(R) 2008 R2, Windows Server(R) 2012, or Windows Server(R) 2012 R2 
  "User Account Control" window is displayed and differs depending on current user permission.
  Under this condition, please click "Allow" if you are a member of the Administrators
  group. Otherwise, you should input administrator password and then click "OK" button.

  In addition, "Program Compatibility Assistant" window is displayed 
  when quitting Setup Utility Tools. 
  When "This program is installed correctly." is selected, 
  this window will not be displayed next time.

The driver and readme.txt are stored under the folder of each OS 
given below.
The Cautions/Limitations on the driver are described in readme.txt.
See the readme file before installing the driver.

   PCL6 Driver
        \PCL


---------------------
3. File Configuration
---------------------
DATAACCESS.DLL
DELPRN.EXE
DOASADMIN.EX_
FXEZDLL.DLL
FXEZRES.DLL
FXEZSUTINI.DLL
FXEZUI.DLL
MAKEDISK.EXE
PATH.INI
SETUP.EX_
SUT.INI
UNINST.EXE
VERUP.EXE
HELP(FXEZHELPEN.CHM,FXEZHELPKO.CHM,FXEZHELPSC.CHM,FXEZHELPTC.CHM)
README.TXT


------------------------------------------------
4. Version Improvements
------------------------------------------------

This section describes the modifications made for each upgraded 
version.

[Modifications from Ver 1.0.0]
* Resolved the situation where the driver cannot be installed using 
  the Setup Tool created on floppy disk.
* Resolved the situation where ports not supported by the tool are 
  listed when selecting the output destination port with the Setup 
  Disk Creation Tool.
* Resolved the situation where text are not displayed correctly in 
  the message.
* Resolved the situation where ports not supported by the tool are 
  listed when adding the output destination port with the Setup Disk 
  Creation Tool.

[Modifications from Ver 1.2.8]
*Improved the problem where the setting file were not created correctly 
 when Setup Tool is created in a floppy disk.

[Improvements from Ver 1.4.2]
*Improved the problem where the driver cannot be deleted with the Uninstallation
 Tool when only the shared printer is installed.
*Improved the problem where the driver cannot be deleted with the Uninstallation
 Tool after the printer icon had been deleted.
 
[Modifications from Ver 2.0.4]
*Setup Utility Tools are upgraded to support Windows Vista(R).

[Modifications from Ver 3.0.5]
*You will be able to specify [Run setup without displaying its screen] and
 [Allow general users to run setup] by the Setup Disk Creation Tool.
*You will not be able to specify the floppy disk as the creation destination
 folder by the Setup Disk Creation Tool.

[Modifications from Ver 3.1.1]
*Setup Utility Tools are upgraded to support Windows(R) 7.

[Modifications from Ver 3.1.2]
*Fixed the bug of the registry being inappropriately deleted when deleting network 
printer by Uninstallation Tool / Icon Deletion Tool.

[Modifications from Ver 3.2.2]
*Improved the problem of user details setup not being inherited in Setup Tool.

[Modifications from Ver 3.3.0]
*The setup disk can now be run even when the folder where it has been stored is assigned to a network drive.
*Resolved the situation where there is no response when printer icon is being created using the Setup Tool.

----------------------------
5. Cautions/Limitations
----------------------------

** Cautions when running the tools other than from the CD-ROM (such 
   as using the tools from the HDD)

When copying the tools to other mediums such as HDD, copy the folder 
"EzInst" and each driver folder in the CD-ROM in the
directories given below.

Note that the tools only operate in the following directories:

|-- PCL                Stores the PCL6 drivers for each OS
|      |------Win95
|      |------Win98_Me
|      |------Nt40
|      |------i386
|      |------amd64
|
|--- EzInst            Stores the complete set of Setup Utility Tools


** Cautions/Limitations

* Selecting NDS Queue
  (When using Windows NT(R) 4.0, Windows(R) 2000, Windows(R) XP, Windows Vista(R), 
  Windows(R) 7, Windows(R) 8, Windows(R) 8.1, Windows(R) 10, 
  Windows Server(R) 2003, Windows Server(R) 2008, Windows Server(R) 2008 R2, 
  Windows Server(R) 2012 or Windows Server(R) 2012 R2)

  Printing cannot be performed if a port/queue on the NDS tree that 
  does not exist in the destination port is selected in the Setup Disk 
  Creation Tool.


* Adding Multiple TCP/IP Direct Print Utility Ports (When using 
  Windows(R) 95, Windows(R) 98 or Windows(R) Me)

  When adding multiple Fuji Xerox TCP/IP Direct Print Utility ports, 
  do not use the following port names for the subsequent added ports.

  * Port names with characters added to the end of an existing port 
    name such as "printer1" or "printer-01", if the existing port 
    name is "printer".

  * Port names with one or more characters taken away from an 
    existing port name, such as "prin" or "print", if the existing 
    port name is "printer".

  * The name is not case sensitive in either case above.

* When "An error has occurred during version upgrade" is displayed 
  during version upgrade

  Delete the print driver with the Uninstallation Tool.  Restart the 
  computer and create a new printer with the driver installation 
  tool.


* Restarting the system during installation/version upgrading (When 
  using Windows NT(R) 4.0, Windows(R) 2000, Windows(R) XP, 
  Windows Vista(R), Windows(R) 7, Windows(R) 8, Windows(R) 8.1, Windows(R) 10, 
  Windows Server(R) 2003, Windows Server(R) 2008, Windows Server(R) 2008 R2, 
  Windows Server(R) 2012 or Windows Server(R) 2012 R2)

  When installing the print driver or upgrading the driver version 
  using the Setup Tool or Upgrade Tool, always restart 
  the computer following the instructions given in the message 
  displayed, before using the print driver.
  Unexpected errors may occur if the computer is not restarted.

* Reflecting the document size using the Setup Tool (When using 
  Windows NT(R) 4.0)

  When a paper unique to the driver is selected, the document size 
  will not be reflected correctly.


* Reflecting the document size using the Setup Tool (When using 
  Windows(R) 2000, Windows(R) XP, Windows Vista(R), Windows(R) 7, Windows(R) 8, 
  Windows(R) 8.1, Windows(R) 10, Windows Server(R) 2003, Windows Server(R) 2008, 
  Windows Server(R) 2008 R2, Windows Server(R) 2012 or Windows Server(R) 2012 R2)

  When a paper unique to the driver is selected, the document size 
  may not be reflected correctly.


* If "Current printer settings may be changed if you install the new 
  driver.  Do you want to continue?" appears when installing 
  driver with the Setup Tool

  Select the check box "Upgrade driver using setup disk" in the 
  Setup Disk Creation Tool, and create a setup disk.

* If Setup Tool is created from a floppy disk using Setup Disk Creation 
  Tool with "Upgrade driver using setup disk" selected

  The verup.exe in the floppy disk cannot be activated. Please activate 
  setup.exe. By activating setup.exe, the print driver will also be 
  upgraded.


* About specifying port for network printer (When using Windows Vista(R), Windows(R) 7, Windows(R) 8, 
  Windows(R) 8.1, Windows(R) 10, Windows Server(R) 2003, Windows Server(R) 2008, 
  Windows Server(R) 2008 R2, Windows Server(R) 2012 or Windows Server(R) 2012 R2)

  Network printer port can't be specified by clicking "Browse" button in 
  "Setup Disk Creation Tool".
  Please input the port name directly in "Network path of printer (P)" 
  text box of "Add printer" dialog.


* Loading printing settings for Setup Tool

  When the Setup Tool is executed with [Allow general users to run setup] specified,
  the printing settings saved in the setup disk will be loaded to the printing settings of the administrator account.

  Even when the Setup Tool is executed without [Allow general users to run setup] specified but with the administrators account specified at the [User Account Control] screen,
  the printing settings saved in the setup disk will be loaded to the printing settings of the administrator account.

  To load settings to the printing settings of all users including users who executed the Setup Tool,
  configure [Printing Defaults] of the printer when creating the setup disk.
  You can set [Printing Defaults] from the [Advanced] tab of the printer properties dialog.


* About driver deleting method  (When using Windows Vista(R), Windows(R) 7, Windows(R) 8, 
  Windows(R) 8.1, Windows(R) 10, Windows Server(R) 2003, Windows Server(R) 2008, 
  Windows Server(R) 2008 R2, Windows Server(R) 2012 or Windows Server(R) 2012 R2)

  To remove drivers from system under Windows Vista(R), Windows(R) 7, Windows(R) 8, 
  Windows(R) 8.1, Windows(R) 10, Windows Server(R) 2003, Windows Server(R) 2008, 
  Windows Server(R) 2008 R2, Windows Server(R) 2012 or Windows Server(R) 2012 R2 completely, 
  please delete drivers and driver package according to the following steps.
  Please be noticed that the driver package will not be deleted
  even if "Uninstallation Tool" is executed.

  (1) For Windows Vista(R), Windows Server(R) 2008

   * Click "Start" and open "Control Panel", then select "Printer" in 
     "Hardware and Sound" panel.
   * Delete printer icon in "Printers and Faxes" folder.
   * Right-click in "Printers and Faxes" folder and select "Run as Administrator". 
     Click "Server Properties" then "Printer Server Properties" window is displayed.
   * Select indicated driver in "Driver" tab and click "Remove" button.
   * Select "Remove driver and driver package.", then click "OK" button.
   * Restart the computer.

  (2) For Windows(R) 7, Windows(R) 8, Windows(R) 8.1, Windows(R) 10, Windows Server(R) 2008 R2, Windows Server(R) 2012 or Windows Server(R) 2012 R2

   * Click the [Start] button, then open [Devices and Printers].
   * Select the printer icon. Click [Remove Device] on the folder tool bar to delete the printer icon.
   * Select any printer icon. Click [Printer server properties] on the folder tool bar to display [Printer Server Properties].
   * From the [Drivers] tab, select a driver to delete, and then click [Remove].
   * Select [Remove Drivers And Package], and then click [OK].
   * Restart the computer.

     If no printer icon appears, display [Printer Server Properties] using the following procedure.

   * Click the [Start] button. Select [Control Panel] and then [Administrative Tools]. Next, open [Printer Management].
   * Click [Printer Servers]. Right click on ["Computer Name" (local)], select [Properties...] to display [Printer Server Properties].

* About restarting the system after executing the Setup Tool when [Run setup
  without displaying its screen] is specified

  Even when the screen is not displayed after executing the Setup Tool to carry out
  installation or version up of the print driver, always restart the system before
  using the print driver. Otherwise, unforeseen error may occur.


* About whether the execution of the Setup Tool is successful when [Run setup
  without displaying its screen] is specified

  If the Setup Tool is executed when [Run setup without displaying its screen] is
  specified, you can determine whether or not the execution is successful by the
  completion code returned: 0 when successful and a non-0 when not.

  Also, please check the reason for the failure by the message displayed when the
  Setup Tool is executed without specifying [Run setup without displaying its screen].


* Using the User Setup Tool when "Allow General User to Execute"is specified

  If a general user places the User Tool in his own desktop to execute it when the user 
  account control is enabled for his OS (Windows Vista  and above), an error may occur.

  When this happens, execute the tool again after allowing "Read & Execute" for the Users 
  group by the security settings of the folder where the User Setup Tool is placed. 


* Notes When Creating Setup Disk Using Setup Disk Creation Tool
  Run the Setup Disk Creation Tool in the same OS as the OS where you run the setup disk.
  Example:
  When running setup disk in Windows 7, run the Setup Disk Creation Tool in another PC with Windows 7.


-------------------
6. Inquiries
-------------------

Please call the number provided in the readme.txt for the relevant 
driver.


"Microsoft", "Windows", "Windows NT", "Windows Server", "Windows Vista" are 
registered trademarks of Microsoft Corporation, U.S.A. in the 
United States and other countries.

